( metal rattling )
( banjo playing faintly )
( steam hissing )
( rumbling )
( dripping )
♪ I 'm just a poor Wayfaring stranger ♪
♪ Traveling through A world of woe ♪
♪ Ain 't no sickness No toil , nor danger ♪
♪ In that bright land To which I go ♪
♪ I 'm going there To see my father ♪
( engine rumbling )
♪ I 'm only going over Jordan I 'm only going over home ♪
( fan whirring )
( humming )
( imitating car accelerating )
♪ I know dark clouds Gonna gather ' round me ♪
♪ I know my way Is rough and steep ♪
( humming intensifies )
( increases volume )
( humming louder )
( stereo volume increases )
♪ I 'm only going over Jordan ♪
♪ I 'm only going over home ♪
- ( thuds ) - ( sighs )
man :
( seatbelt clicks )
( tires squeal )
- ( indistinct conversation ) - ( machine beeping )
( clanging )
woman :
woman 2 :
( kisses )
( electronic music playing )
( indistinct chatter )
- ( chatter increasing ) - ( whistling )
( " Doing It To Death " by The Kills playing on speakers )
( car engine revs )
( engine rumbles )
( song continues )
( song fades )
( grunts )
Ah !
( snorts )
( yelps , groans )
( tense music playing )
man :
( car alarm chirps )
man : Alexia !
( sighs )
( exhales )
( gurgling )
( grunts )
( mutters )
( groans )
( loud metallic bang )
( loud bang )
( gasps )
( moans )
( groans )
( panting )
( exhales )
( stomach gurgles )
( groans softly )
( waves lapping )
( gasps )
( laughs )
( groans )
( whimpers )
( grunts )
( gasps , groans )
( rattles )
( muffled yelp )
( muffled scream )
( grunts )
( knock on door )
Ah !
( groans )
( screams )
- ( squelches ) - ( yelps )
- ( grunts ) - ( groans )
( upbeat ' 60 's Italian pop music playing )
( grunts )
Ah !
Romain :
( grunting )
( choking )
( loud crunch )
( sound muffles )
( sound resumes )
( song continues )
( woman whimpering )
man :
( sighs )
( exhales )
( groans )
- ( yells ) - ( grunts )
( woman screams )
( yells )
( grunts )
( yelling )
- ( woman whimpers ) - ( footsteps hurrying away )
( waves lapping )
( emergency brake clicks )
woman 3 :
( police radio chatter )
( indistinct PA announcement )
( objects clatter )
( water running )
( grunts softly )
( grunts )
( groans )
( exhales )
( yelps )
Ah !
( spits )
( groans )
( moans , exhales )
( laughs )
( indistinct PA announcement )
( man on walkie talkie )
( stifled sob )
( sobs )
( seatbelt clicks )
( groans )
( sighs )
( knocking )
Whoa !
( lock turns )
( grunts )
( strains )
( moans )
( groans softly )
( clippers buzzing )
( food sizzling )
( laughs )
Huh ?
( fork clatters )
( lock rattles )
( " She 's Not There " by the Zombies playing on stereo )
( grunting )
( chuckling )
( panting )
( door slams )
( groans )
( grunts )
( boys chatting indistinctly )
( boys laughing )
boy :
( boy making kissing sounds )
boy 2 :
boy 3 :
boy 1 :
( clippers click on , off )
( clippers buzz )
( exterior door opens )
Vincent :
Whoa , whoa , whoa .
( oxygen tank hisses )
( sobs )
( thuds )
( singing ) ♪ Da , da-da-da , da-da-da Macarena ♪
♪ Da , da-da-da , da-da-da Cosa buena ♪
♪ Da , da-da-da , da-da-da Macarena ♪
♪ Oh , Macarena ♪
( blowing )
♪ Da , da-da-da , da-da-da Macarena ♪
♪ Da , da-da-da , da-da-da Cosa buena ♪
♪ Oh , Macarena ♪
( blowing )
♪ Da , da-da-da , da-da-da Macarena ♪
♪ Da , da-da-da , da-da-da Cosa buena ♪
( woman inhales )
( woman grunts )
Rayane :
Rayane : Madam ?
( engine starts )
( siren blares )
( chuckles )
( " Lighthouse " by Future Islands playing )
( song continues )
( inaudible )
( sound muffles )
( sound resumes )
( song continues )
( exhales )
( scratching )
( grunts )
( scratching continues )
Ah .
( gasps )
( grunts )
( breathing heavily )
( sobs )
( groans )
( grunting in pain )
( panicked breathing )
( gasping )
( groaning , gasping )
Huh ?
( moans in pain )
( grunts )
( whimpers )
( gasps )
( door slams )
( upbeat theme song playing )
Vincent :
( distant explosion )
( debris falling )
- ( loud thud ) - Ah !
( explosion )
( all clamoring )
( indistinct yelling )
( soft grunt )
( grunts )
( knock on door )
( door closes )
- ( techno music playing ) - ( men yelling )
( song fades )
( men cheering )
( chanting )
( all yelling )
♪ I 'm just a poor Wayfaring stranger ♪
♪ Traveling through This world of woe ♪
♪ Ain 't no sickness No toil , nor danger ♪
♪ In that bright land To which I go ♪
♪ I 'm going there To see my Father ♪
( men booing )
♪ I 'm only going over Jordan ♪
♪ I 'm only going over home ♪
♪ I know dark clouds Gonna gather ' round me ♪
♪ I know my way Be rough and steep ♪
♪ Yet beautiful fields Lie just before me ♪
♪ Where God 's redeemed Their vigils keep ♪
♪ I 'm going there To meet my mother ♪
♪ I 'm going there No more to roam ♪
( door opens )
♪ I 'm only going over home ♪
♪ I 'll soon be free From every trial ♪
♪ This form shall rest Beneath the sun ♪
♪ I 'll drop this cross of Self-denial ♪
♪ And enter in That home with God ♪
♪ I 'm goin ' home To meet my Savior ♪
( song fades )
( door slams )
- ( heavy breathing ) - ( rhythmic pounding )
( moaning )
( groans )
( panting )
( sobbing )
( gasping )
( grunts )
Ah !
( heaving )
( straining )
( pushing )
( gasps )
( groans )
( dramatic music playing )
( panting )
( yelps )
( groans )
( whimpering )
( grunting )
( grunts , gasps )
( whimpers )
( grunts )
( straining )
( pushing )
( grunting )
( straining )
( screams )
( grunting )
( baby cries )
( baby continues crying )
( blowing )
( baby gurgles , cries )
( snips )
( baby cries )
( continues crying )
( dramatic music playing )